

# Kevin Nathanael Taufiek

- +6285155218871
- ★ kevin.taufiek@gmail.com
- https://kevinnathanaeltaufiek.github.io/
- Depok, Indonesia

#### SUMMARY

Currently a second-year computer science student at Bina Nusantara University, Software Engineering Stream program. Joined Binus Student Learning Community Organization (BSLC) as an IT Support activist and mentor. Understand the basics of computer science such as problem-solving, programming algorithms, and so on as well as soft skills such as leadership, communication, and collaboration. Became "Beasiswa Juara" scholarship awardee and became a scholarship mentor for 2 periods. Have an interest in Web Development (Front End and Back End ) and Mobile Development. Have strong desire to become a developer.

### EXPERIENCE

11/2020 - Present

#### **IT Support**

Binus Student Learning Community

- Ensure the content on the organization's website is appropriate
- · Manage data and content on website pages
- Responsible for data and content in the organization

10/2020 - 07/2021

### **Scholarship Mentor**

Bina Nusantara University

- Managed study time and mentoring in study groups
- Assist & mentored mentees to achieve better grades
- · Motivate mentees to keep develop their skill

07/2019 - 08/2020

## **Education Counselor**

Bina Nusantara University

- · Participated in campus tour events
- · Help students to find college majors that are suitable for them
- Promote scholarship program

## EDUCATION

2023

## **Computer Science**

Bina Nusantara University

Bachelor

- Became "Beasiswa Juara" scholarship awardee
- Became a scholarship mentor for 2 periods
- · Got a perfect GPA in the fourth semester

## CERTIFICATES

06/2021 - Present SoloLearn PHP Course

07/2020 - Present HackerRank Problem Solving Certificate

07/2021 - Present Coding Studio Laravel Course

## SKILLS

CSS Intermediate Java Advanced Intermediate Bootstrap С Advanced Intermediate **UI** Design PHP Intermediate **UX** Design Beginner Intermediate C# Intermediate Database Design JavaScript Beginner SQL Advanced **Object Oriented Programming** Advanced / 00P Intermediate MySQL Intermediate **Data Structures** SQL Server Advanced Laravel Intermediate **SQLite** Intermediate ASP.NET Intermediate Android Studio Intermediate HTML Advanced API Intermediate

## LANGUAGES

Indonesia Native English Intermediate